macxdvd.com 2019-03-31

# MacXDVD Software Privacy Policy

MacXDVD cares about the privacy of your data and are committed to complying with the GDPR when it becomes enforceable on May 25, 2018. Therefore, in our Privacy Policy, we explain what information we collect, how do we use them, how we protect your information and your choices. 

## What Personal Information Does MacXDVD Collect Or Receive? 

MacXDVD may collect or receive the following personal information from you: Contact Information (such as name, email address, mailing address, or phone number). How do we collect your information? 

**The information you provide us**

**1\. Make Payment**

When you purchase products from our site, your billing is handled by our third-party service provider, 2Checkout. The service provider is acting as our agent; thus, you will be making your purchase from the service provider directly, and not from us. We do not store credit card or other financial information. We only collect contact information from you that we pass through to the payment processor to facilitate the transaction. For more information, you can contact our providers as set forth in their privacy notices.

**2\. Sign up for our newsletter**

If you wish to sign up for our newsletter, you will have to enter your email address in the appropriate field. We will then store your email address in order to send you our newsletter.

**3\. Register a product**

When you are registering our software, you will be asked to provide a valid email to successfully activate the program for warranty claim purposes.

**4\. Request for Support**

when you contact us here, we will store your email address, your name, or your telephone number, if you have provided it, in order to answer your questions. We will also store your message so that we can process your request.

**5\. Campaigns**

In some of our campaigns, you will be asked to fill your email address to join the survey, contest or giveaway offer to obtain the participation qualification, which is also necessary to deliver the prizes to you. 

**6.Third Party Data**

MacXDVD may receive data about customer information, marketing campaigns and other matters related to our business from affiliates, resellers, partners or others that we use to make our own information better or more useful.

**Information we collect automatically when you use our services.**

**1\. Cookies:**

We may use cookies. A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to your browser from a web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. If you revisit our website, our web server will recognize the cookie and provide information about your last visit. Usually, you can modify the settings of your browser to accept or reject all cookies or as an alternative to being notified when a cookie is set. We may use cookies to provide a more personalized and user-friendly visit to our website and to help us track user traffic patterns. A cookie cannot read your hard disk or other cookie files. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

**2\. Google Analytics**

For the purpose of customizing and continually optimizing our pages, we use Google Analytics. It is an analytics tool that helps website owners understand how visitors engage with their website through a variety of reports in order to improve the website. Like many services, Google Analytics uses first-party cookies to track visitor interactions, as in MacXDVD's case, where they are used to collect information about how visitors use our site. We use this information to compile reports and to improve our site. Cookies contain information that is transferred to your computer's hard drive. 

These cookies are used to store information, such as the time the current visit occurred, whether the visitor has been to the site before, and what site referred the visitor to the web page. Google Analytics collects information anonymously. It reports website trends without identifying individual visitors. You can opt out of Google Analytics without affecting how you visit our site – for more information on opting out of being tracked by Google Analytics across all websites you use, please visit Google. 

**3\. Log files**

Like many other websites, MacXDVD makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, type of browser used, date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and the number of clicks. MacXDVD uses this information to analyze trends, administer the site, track movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information, are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

## Children's Privacy

MacXDVD does not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13. If we determine we have collected personal information from a child younger than 13 years of age, we will take reasonable measures to remove that information from our systems. If you are under the age of 13, please do not submit any personal information through the Site and/or Products. We encourage parents and legal guardians to monitor their children's Internet usage and to help enforce this Policy by instructing their children never to provide personal information through the Sites and/or Products without their permission.

## How Do We Use the Information 

Other than with respect to the exceptions below, we do not share personal information with third parties. We use personal information to improve and market our products and for shaping our external communication and messaging efforts. We may use the information we collect in the following ways:

• To personalize your experience and to allow us to deliver the type of content and product offerings in which you are most interested.

• To improve our website in order to better serve you.

• To allow us to better service you in responding to your customer service requests.

• To notify contest winners and award prizes.

• To quickly process your transactions.

• To ask for ratings and reviews of services or products

• To follow up with them after correspondence (email or phone inquiries)

From time to time, we may want to contact you with information about product announcements, software updates, and special offers. We also may want to contact you with information about products and services from our business partners. We only send marketing communications to users with your prior consent.

## How Do We Protect Your Information?

Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. In addition, all sensitive/credit information you supply is encrypted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology.

## Third-party Disclosure

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your Personally Identifiable Information unless we provide users with advance notice. This does not include website hosting partners and other parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or serving our users, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release information when it's release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

## How to Change or Delete Your Information

If you wish to access, update, correct or request deletion of your personal data, you can do so by contacting us. You can always object to processing the of your personal data, please ask us to restrict processing of your personal data or request a data export. Again, you can do so by contacting us. You have the right to complain to a data protection authority about our collection and use of your personal data. For more info, please contact your local data protection authority.

## Questions

If you have any questions, comments or just want to say hi, feel free to write an email to [support@macxdvd.com](mailto:support@macxdvd.com)

The last update to our Privacy Statement was posted on May 25, 2018

.
